Being a black billionaire is not success. It's assimilation. What I mean
is that the concept of success is very different depending on what you believe in.
Now, if capitalism is what drives you, then her being a billionaire is why she's successful.
If, you know, ambition and achievement is what drives you, then her having a goal of getting a TV show
and then that show garnering a high level of viewership, then that's what makes you successful.
But you can do that and not be a billionaire. You follow? The level of money that you have
is not, in my opinion, the determiner of the success. It means that you were able to function
within the capitalist framework at a level that was a high level. And by the way, this also doesn't
mean you're smart. I know some people think that because people made money that they're smart. No,
they're good at making money. Capitalism does not require you to be an intellectual. It requires you
to be good at making money. And that is a very specific skill. I know a lot of dumb millionaires.
A lot. The thing that I want to point out though is just because you received the money
doesn't make you a billionaire. What made you a billionaire was hoarding the money.
So when we talk about success, I don't believe that we should measure it on how much money you've
hoarded. I believe success should not be measured on money at all, but more so on what you have been
able to achieve inwardly and outwardly for your community in doing so. There is no reason anybody
should be a billionaire while people can't eat. And I know that there are Black people in this
country who will say, oh, how dare you, Amanda? And you can how dare me all you want. Because at the
end of the day, none of that money has made it easier for Black people to not get killed in this
country for being Black. Right? Exactly.